Viktor Savitskiy

Phone: 262.960.0775 Email: savitvi8@gmail.com

In:www.linkedin.com/in/viktor-savitskiy-711a7a77/ Github: viktorsavitskiy

OBJECTIVE SUMMARY

Web Developer specializing in both front-end and back-end development. Experienced with a variety of programming languages including, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Ruby, PHP, and MySQL. Detailed oriented and able to solve problems creatively. Highly interested in pursuing a junior to entry-level developer position.

EXPERIENCE

AT&T, Workflow Developer; Arlington Heights, IL - May 2016 - August 2016

Worked on the development of SASHA a web application used by AT&T call center agents.

Responsibilities:

- Implement changes to existing workflows.
- Debug and trace down defects for existing workflows.
- Perform unit and regression testing on all new/modified workflows.
- Perform production deployments of workflows on a regularly scheduled basis.
- Implemented custom styling on the front end of SASHA using HTML, CSS, and jQuery
- Utilized MySQL databases to efficiently add, remove and modify support ticket data
- Assisted in quality assurance and release testing, allowing the team to include additional fixes during software release.

Guard Llama, Wordpress/PHP Developer (Intern); Chicago, IL - March 2016 - April 2016 Developed a reseller portal using Wordpress and PHP, for users to sell personal security devices for Guard Llama.

Responsibilities:

- Worked with developers and designers to create themes and plugins for Wordpress.
- Integrated API's into Wordpress.
- Setup hosting service and databases for Wordpress.

SKILLS

Programming Languages		Development Tools	Content Management Systems
- HTML - CSS	- jQuery - PHP	- MS SQL Server 2012 - Wordpress - Eclipse - OpenCart	
- JavaScript	- jQuery	- Git/Github	

EDUCATION

Startup Institute - Web Development Track, 2016

Gateway Technical College - Technical Degree in Web Development, 2014 - 2016